DYNAMITE KISS
Mr. Gong.
Mr. Gong, are you okay?
Wake up!
Oh no…
Mr. Gong!
Mr. Gong…
Mr. Gong?
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Thank goodness.
Do you know how scared I was
that something might've happened to you?
I need to…
tell you something.
There are no particular reasons
as to why I like you.
I just like you for who you are.
You're Go Da-rim.
That's why I like you.
I love you.
I like you too.
After leaving you in Jeju like that,
I've always missed you
and thought about you.
Do you mean it?
It was so hard seeing your face every day
while feeling like that.
I'm sorry for taking so long
to tell you how I feel.
I…
love you too.
Ji-hyeok!
Ji-hyeok, let me see you!
Eyes, nose, mouth. They're all there.
You're safe now!
I'm fine.
Let go of me.
-Excuse me, can you check him out?
-Sure.
I told you I'm fine. Jeez.
Please hurry!
-How's your breathing?
-It's fine.
Ji-hyeok, breathe.
Is there anything for him to drink?
Do you want some water?
EPISODE 11
I've decided to believe
that you're serious
about wanting to help.
Remain calm!
-Don't rush!
-Remain calm!
Don't rush!
Don't rush.
But why are you taking it this far?
Is it really just for money?
I detest Ji-hyeok just as much.
Why?
Because you lost all the companies
you were trying to acquire
to Ji-hyeok?
So it's just an inferiority complex, huh?
No, I respect those who are competent.
But that punk
has such an arrogant look in his eyes.
His eyes?
"I succeeded without my father's help."
"I fought fair and square."
"I'm nothing like you."
There's something oddly dismissive
about his gaze,
and it really gets on my nerves.
I think I'll only feel better
after I properly crush him.
Acting all lofty
as if he were being guided
by some noble principle.
It is obnoxious.
It's been a while
since we were on the same page.
We're a team now, right?
They found an ID badge
that belonged to a Taeyu C&T
labor union member near the office.
I suspect he was one of the workers
who were laid off recently.
Taeyu C&T is infamous
for its labor-management conflicts.
We somehow ended up in the line of fire.
I almost forgot.
Ji-hyeok.
About Ms. Go Da-rim…
What are you going to do now?
Make it clear now.
What?
Don't tell me you saw it.
-I did.
-All of it?
Yes, I saw everything.
Well, that was…
Gyeong-min, I think you may have
gotten the wrong idea.
-I--
-Wrong idea, my foot.
We all saw Ms. Go
run in there to save you.
Who would risk their life
to save their boss from a burning building
in this day and age?
You should know how blessed you are.
So stop acting like a jerk
and snapping at her
just because you're the team leader,
and be nice to her.
She's not just an employee.
She's your savior.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Eat your porridge.
Thank you for the porridge.
-Wow, what is all this?
-Eat up.
No, you can't!
Life may be tough,
but this isn't the answer.
What the heck? Who are you?
Let go of me!
Let's do that again.
Do you know how worried I was?
I didn't know if you were being chased
or had gotten into some sort of accident.
Do you know how hard I searched for you?
I know.
You're nice to me
only because I'm a member of your team.
But still,
I find myself
being swayed.
I'm…
not a good person.
Sorry?
I'm also…
swayed.
Stay with me.
Don't go.
I don't want you to go.
There are no particular reasons
as to why I like you.
I just like you for who you are.
You're Go Da-rim.
That's why I like you.
I love you.
This is insane.
Let's see.
It doesn't suit me.
Yeah.
This doesn't suit me either.
Yes?
I'm screwed.
I'm so screwed.
Today must be an important day.
I just thought it was a shame
that all these clothes
in my sister's wardrobe
were just gathering dust.
I see.
Would you like me to pick something out?
Sure.
Not this.
How about this?
I think that looks nice.
You think so?
Don't you think it's a bit too short?
I thought something simple
would be better.
You think so?
I suppose this is something
Ji-hyeok would like.
Goodness, what do I know?
I should just trust your judgment.
-Good morning, Mr. Gong.
-There he is.
-Mr. Gong.
-Good morning, Mr. Gong.
-Good morning.
NATURAL BEBE
Isn't Mr. Gong so handsome?
I wish I could join the TF team.
I'd get to see that face every day.
He really is a feast for the eyes.
I'm so jealous.
I want to join the TF team too.
Hold on.
You caught me off guard.
We need to be careful at work.
Be careful?
About what?
There were so many people in the elevator.
You can't just hold my hand like that.
Your hand?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I couldn't help myself
because you're so pretty.
Oh my goodness!
-My gosh, they're so pretty!
-They are!
-They're beautiful.
-I can't believe it.
Seriously, this is incredible.
-My goodness.
-Just look at that note.
"To my precious four-leaf clover."
"Thank you.
I promise to only make you happier."
He's so cool.
Mr. Kim Seon-u is such a romantic.
Someone might think
you two just started dating.
He must've sent it to cheer you up,
considering how the exhibition wrapped up.
I'd be happy if my husband
did a quarter of what he does.
In your dreams.
A husband like Mr. Kim
is rarer than winning the lottery.
He's handsome, talented, and doting.
Only someone as lucky and blessed
as Da-rim could land a guy like him.
Now, now.
You're still on the clock.
Let's get back to work.
Please.
-Yes, sir.
He's such a killjoy.
Gosh, they're so pretty.
Come in.
Thank you
for the flowers.
You didn't have to send me flowers.
Thank goodness no one else caught on.
Gosh.
Even if no one else caught on,
I sent them so you can take note.
Of what?
That today is day one of our relationship.
Gosh, you're too much.
I think they all left to buy something.
I need to head out soon.
I don't think I'll see you
for the rest of the day.
Well, it can't be helped.
You can't do it here.
Not here…
We have so much to do.
I know.
Oh no. They're back. What should we do?
Hold on. Maybe I should…
Did you reach out?
-Ms. Go Da-rim!
-Oh my.
Do you call this work?
I'm sorry.
-I'm really sorry, sir.
-Poor Da-rim.
What set him off this time?
He's such a jerk.
Oh no.
Are you free this weekend?
Yes, I am. Why do you ask?
Let's go on a date.
Is there anything you want to eat?
We can go get something to eat.
A movie sounds good too.
Or maybe even a trip.
It's not like Da-rim started the fire.
We're also upset about it.
He's just taking it too far.
I've had enough of it.
I need to get in there.
You'll only make things worse now.
I'll go and talk to him in a bit.
Come here. Quickly.
-Should I go now?
-What's he doing?
What is it? What's he doing?
Overnight is even better.
Overnight?
Isn't that a bit too soon?
Don't you remember what happened in Jeju?
We were totally--
All right, okay. I hear you.
I'll think about it.
Just trust me and follow my lead!
-Oh my goodness.
-Oh dear.
-Get in there and stop him.
-Go stop him.
Should I get in there now?
Something serious is about to happen.
Unfortunately,
the fire is the issue in the spotlight
instead of the exhibition.
"How could an environmental campaign
ignore fire safety?"
"You might as well just drop everything."
Such snide reactions have been prevalent.
How could you handle the situation
so unprofessionally?
Sir.
Mr. Gong was also in danger that day.
For now,
Taeyu C&T has agreed
to announce that the culprit
was one of its former labor union members,
not any mismanagement on our part--
A little late for that, don't you think?
Has that person been apprehended?
Well, not yet.
Then a laborer being the culprit
is still only speculation.
Nothing has been confirmed.
A further investigation has to be--
No, just leave it be.
They agreed to take the fall.
Let's conclude today's meeting here.
How are you feeling?
-Better?
-Yeah.
Thanks for your concern.
I didn't do anything.
You should be thanking Ms. Go.
I heard she risked her life to save you.
You two must be close.
Just like any team leader and member.
I'm envious.
It must be nice to have
a team member like that.
All right then.
Take care of yourself.
Hey.
Hey. Do you have what I asked for?
Yeah.
These are all the CCTV footage
from inside and outside
the art hall for the past week.
Thanks.
You're right. It's a bit suspicious.
If he managed to reach the office
without being caught on the CCTVs,
that means he knew the layout
of the art hall well.
I'm sure
he scoped the place out beforehand.
Then he must be in here somewhere.
Are you going to watch
a whole week's worth of footage?
There's going to be
a ton of people on there.
Will you even recognize him?
I definitely remember his eyes.
You must be upset about the exhibition
ending in such a way.
It's fine.
I'm just thankful no one got hurt.
How's Mr. Gong?
Is he all right?
Yeah, he says he's fine.
Listen, Seon-u.
About what you told me last time--
I just remembered
I have an urgent project to finish up.
I need to send it over
by tomorrow morning.
Sorry, Da-rim. Let's talk later.
Right, okay.
Of course, work comes first.
I can clean this up later.
All right then.
I'll get going.
-Bye.
This looks delicious.
It's so good.
The egg is so soft.
Hold on.
Who's softer?
The egg or me?
Are you serious?
Answer me.
The egg or me?
Of course…
it's the egg.
I wouldn't call you the soft type.
Then what am I?
You're…
a bit more
of the sexy type.
I guess.
So that's what I am.
Okay. Eat up.
You know,
it's so nice to be able to
go on lunch dates like this.
I think office romances are great.
-Are you enjoying it?
-Yeah.
When I start my own company,
I'm going to make office romances
a requirement for all employees.
What?
When I woke up this morning,
I was so excited to go to work.
If every employee were as eager
to get to work as I am,
just imagine how productive they'd be.
Do that at your own company.
What if someone from the office sees us?
Do you know how anxious I am?
That's why
I chose a place far away from the office.
So smart, right?
Yes.
Thank you for lunch.
I'll be sure to treat you next time.
Should we take a walk before heading back?
Sure, why not?
Come on.
What if someone sees us?
But what can I do?
I like you so much, it's killing me.
-I mean, I guess we can't let you die.
-Come on. It'll be fine.
I made sure no one we know is around.
Such nice weather today.
-No, Nan-suk.
-No.
Did we have to come this far for lunch?
Trust me. It's a really good place.
-Most sandwiches are so small.
-What's going on?
I hate thin sandwiches.
Sandwiches need to be thick.
-They do?
-Damn it.
-Really?
-That won't be filling.
Isn't that Ms. Go?
Hello, everyone!
Didn't you say you were meeting a friend?
Oh, they had something urgent come up.
Something urgent?
Just a second. Please.
You were stood up.
Oh no, that's too bad.
Did you have lunch already?
There's this new sandwich place nearby.
-That's where we're headed.
-Really?
You have to go this way to get there.
-What?
-I think it's this way.
There's a sinkhole over there.
Come in.
Mr. Gong.
Would you like to have dinner
at my place tonight?
Our mothers made dumplings,
and they wanted you to come over.
I don't think I can today.
Why not?
I'm on a treasure hunt.
I never knew there was a place like this
in the company.
I only know about it
because the CSR team leader told me.
By the way, you don't need to help me.
You can't go through all this by yourself.
Not to mention, you have to find it
without getting caught.
So of course, I'm going to help you.
Who's there?
Oh, there's no one.
-He hasn't left yet.
-Really?
What are you doing?
Hold on, he's still there. Be quiet.
Okay.
Oh, come on. What are you doing?
The more I learn about your mother,
the more amazing she is.
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR KIM IN-AE
LEADS THE TREE-PLANTING CAMPAIGN
I'm sure
prioritizing the company's
social responsibilities
couldn't have been easy back then.
My mom
wasn't looking to just sell baby products.
She wanted to create a world
that ensured children's happiness.
It looks like that led to
a lot of conflict with the board members.
She's a total warrior.
It looks that way.
MANAGEMENT MEETING MINUTES
I always thought of my mom
as someone weak I needed to protect.
She's incredibly strong.
She's even fighting now.
So,
I hope you don't try to shoulder
all of this on your own anymore.
Your mother told me
about your childhood.
Why did she waste your time like that?
It wasn't a waste of time.
Thanks to her, all my questions about you
were answered.
What questions did you have?
You could've asked me.
I wondered why someone
who has everything and more
sometimes had a wounded look in his eyes.
I wondered why someone who's more mature
and reliable than anyone
sometimes…
looked like a lost child.
I thought about…
how scared and tough
it must've been for that child.
You must've been…
really lonely.
It's okay.
You're okay.
You're not alone anymore.
I'll always be by your side.
From now on until forever.
I'll be here to hold you,
adore you,
and protect you.
And…
we're going to tackle all of it together.
The hard stuff,
the scary stuff,
and the loneliness.
All of it.
Thank you.
Goodness.
Mr. Kim?
-Oh, hello.
-Hello.
Did you go grocery shopping
on your way home?
-Yes.
-Where's Da-rim?
She should be at home.
By any chance,
did you and Da-rim
receive some good news recently?
Are you two expecting again?
Not at all.
No? Then why did you send
that giant flower basket to the office?
"To my precious four-leaf clover."
"I promise to only make you happier."
My gosh!
It made everyone in the office go crazy!
I almost fainted.
Da-rim was ecstatic too.
I'm glad she liked it.
Seon-u.
Hey.
Did you pick up groceries?
Yeah.
Jun wanted bulgogi for dinner.
I see.
Seon-u.
I have something to tell you.
-Da-rim.
-Yeah?
Let me speak first.
Okay.
Remember when I told you that I liked you?
Yeah?
Messing with you is not fun at all.
What do you mean?
It felt like I was the only one losing out
from this whole married couple charade.
I thought it was unfair, so I wanted to
mess with you by saying I liked you,
but I can't do this anymore.
It's making my skin crawl.
You were messing with me
when you said you had feelings for me?
Yeah, I was.
What?
Wait.
That stroked your ego, didn't it?
I can't just stand by and let that happen.
I mean, even if it's just a joke,
some lines shouldn't be crossed.
Are you kidding me?
Hey.
That hurts.
Hey,
do you know how worried I was
about hurting your feelings?
You're my only friend.
Do you even know
how terrified I was of losing you?
Why would you be scared?
You're stronger than me.
Come here. You're dead meat.
-Wait. Stop.
-Do you know what you put me through?
-Hold on a second.
-I should beat you up right now!
-You'd better stop right there!
-Come on, it was just a joke.
No, you're looking down too much.
Look up.
Too much.
Just a bit. There you go.
You have no energy right now.
You need to be more upbeat.
Lift that spirit.
The expression is crucial.
You want to look poised, chic, and lovely.
There you go.
No. Your head is tilted. Straighten it.
Maintain posture. Up.
Did Father leave already?
Yeah.
He has a lot to deal with
after the fire reignited union issues.
I can't face our in-laws.
Did Ji-hyeok say anything?
He just wants to find the culprit
as soon as possible.
It's not even a big deal.
We should just move on.
What do you mean it's not a big deal?
I worked really hard on that exhibition.
I'm sure this was a malicious attack
meant to sabotage me.
Hey, snap out of it.
Who'd start a fire to sabotage you?
Don't say that.
She's made substantial progress.
The visitors in the morning
and the VIPs who received the pamphlets
are very interested in purchasing.
Really? Is that true?
He's quite good
for a no-name photographer.
You have a good eye for things,
just like me.
Prepare for a second showing
after the restoration.
Thanks, Mom! I promise to do my best.
Great, let's keep up that lively spirit.
Head up!
What's with the long face?
This is good news.
Aren't you excited?
Sure.
I'm glad to hear it.
I hurriedly came here to tell you
before telling Ji-hyeok.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Consoling you.
What's with the random consolation?
Just be quiet.
It's obvious
you're in desperate need of some.
Ms. Go rejected you, didn't she?
How did you know?
It's only going to get harder from now on.
You have to pretend like you're fine,
as if nothing happened.
It's heartbreaking
when you put on a brave face,
but it goes unrecognized.
But you should be thankful.
You have a woman of my stature
patiently waiting for you.
This is just too unfair for me.
Go and get me some coffee or something.
I refuse to leave with nothing today.
Go on.
The Green Forest Campaign
can be taken off your hands now, Ji-hyeok.
-The marketing team will take over.
-Pardon?
As in my team, sir?
This campaign is a long-term project.
To maintain strategic direction
and established partnerships,
it'd be best for my team to continue--
That's exactly why he wants
another team to take over.
The Mother TF Team
is made up of fixed-term interns.
Even if some become full-time,
it'll be difficult to keep the team.
To keep the campaign going,
shouldn't we have
a permanent team dedicated to it?
You don't need to worry about that.
If you entrust it to me,
I promise to give it my all.
Then how about
sending the Mother TF Team
to support the CS team?
-The CS team?
-Yes.
They can listen to customers' needs
and requests firsthand
and utilize that knowledge
in product development.
I believe that'll benefit
Mr. Gong in the end as well.
Sure. Sounds good.
How did you ever think of that?
The CS team has the highest turnover rate
in the company.
I wonder if those stay-at-home moms
will even survive ten days there.
Have the CS team transfer over
the most problematic
blacklisted customer cases
to the Mother TF Team.
I'm going to get rid of the whole team.
PROVIDING WORDS OF EMPATHY
THAT RESONATE WITH CUSTOMERS!
HEARING OUT THE CUSTOMERS
TO RESPOND WITH EMPATHY!
What a fun way to put it.
What can I help you with today?
SERVICE LEVEL: 91%
RESPONSE RATE: 97%
CALLS IN PROGRESS: 45
Dry cleaning?
Yes, I can submit the request, but…
I understand you're an influencer,
but a refund request
for ten times the original amount…
I'm sorry.
Ma'am, I actually own
that same luxury bag.
It's not that expensive--
Are we sure we're still in Korea?
I'm speaking Korean,
but they don't understand me.
Damn that influencer,
influenza, or whatever.
I mean, I can curse too.
Unbelievable.
I need a drink.
What are you doing?
Relieving stress.
I'm going to buy everything in my cart.
Are you nuts?
Are you going to blow a month's pay
after working half a day?
Doing this is the only thing
keeping me from a breakdown.
Wait, where did Go-eun go?
One of the customers earlier
said that there was no way
I could be a decent mom.
Who the hell said that?
Don't listen to people like that.
Why would you cry
over someone like that?
I know I shouldn't.
I do, but it was still so upsetting.
Look at me.
Ms. Lee,
you're a great mother.
I can guarantee you that.
Thank you.
The chairman is here.
Please prepare some tea.
Okay.
I'd love to see my daughter-in-law
more frequently.
I'll visit more often, Father.
And I'm sorry for causing you distress
for what happened last time.
Don't be silly. Things like that happen
when running a business.
Let Chairman Yu know
not to worry about us as well.
I will.
I can see that Ji-hyeok
is generous and understanding
because he takes after you.
Did they have to
take their acting that far?
Are they trying to win an Oscar or what?
Damn it.
Right?
I should find a dress for the red carpet.
Did you hear all that?
Don't worry. It's all just an act
at the end of the day.
And I actually like someone else.
Someone much more handsome
and cool than Gong Ji-hyeok.
Does a man like that exist?
Mr. Kim.
What, Seon-u?
Wait, then you knew about it too?
That Seon-u and I…
Since we're on the subject,
how about a drink tonight?
Fake wife.
Fake girlfriend.
I think we'd have a lot to talk about.
Cheers.
So you guys just went for it
on the very first day you met?
Yes.
So much for being so indifferent.
Who knew there was such a side to him?
-This is why you can't trust men.
-Oh, let me.
Why do you like Seon-u?
Is he nice to you?
No. He treats me terribly.
He always plays hard to get
and pushes me away.
-It's so tiring.
-Then why do you like him?
I'm jealous of this woman in a photo.
Pardon?
You see,
I've always lived the life
my dad chose for me.
If I fell a little short
of his expectations,
I was dismissed, ignored,
and compared to my older brother.
When my father told me
he didn't expect anything from me anymore
and that my duty would be fulfilled
if I just married Ji-hyeok,
I was honestly so happy.
I thought I could finally be free.
I could sense the freedom
I'd been wanting.
But…
I realized something
when I saw how Mr. Kim looked at children.
What I really wanted wasn't freedom.
It was for someone to look at me
with warm, loving eyes.
I thought if I were with a man like him,
I could also smile brightly
like the woman in the photo one day.
When you say the woman in the photo…
So you liked him
even though you knew from the start?
It made me like him even more.
Because he was still capable
of being so warm
despite failing at love
and being hurt by it.
That's true.
I've known him for over 20 years,
and he's always been like that.
It's pretty amazing.
That's why I decided
to become his windbreaker
in this cold, cruel world
and guard that warmth
for the rest of my life.
For both him and Jun, of course.
I'm relieved.
What?
To be honest,
I was worried
that it might've been a situation
where the daughter of a chaebol family
found out about Seon-u's predicament
and grew curious out of pity.
But I was wrong.
Thank you
for seeing him for who he is.
You probably recognized that in him
because you're just as warmhearted.
But it's not easy to win him over.
He's so odd.
Maybe he doesn't like pretty women.
That could be a possibility.
Totally.
Should we brainstorm
what you can do from now on?
-Cheers.
Let's link our arms and drink!
Let's link…
Ha-yeong!
You should just be my younger sister.
Really? I'd love that!
I've always wanted an older sister.
-My younger sister!
-My older sister!
Hold on, giving allowances
to my younger sister is my thing.
Let's see here.
One, two, three, four…
You don't need to.
I know about your financial struggles.
What are you talking about?
Take it. It's fine.
-I won't take no for an answer.
-You're the best!
You're so cute!
Starting today,
-I'll be Go Ha-yeong.
-No, I'll be Yu Da-rim.
-Those two are okay, right?
-Yu Da-rim!
I hope so.
I didn't expect Ms. Yu to be like this.
Look at you so worried about me.
-No, Ms. Yu, I…
-Why did you drink so much?
-I'm in such a good mood today.
-Yes, Mr. Kim!
I know you should be in bed. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
This is what boyfriends are for.
Ha-yeong!
-Hey, I was going to say earlier…
-Da-rim, the second round is on me.
I'm rich.
What in the world is going on?
They reek of alcohol.
-Mom!
-Please.
Oh my goodness, Ha-yeong too.
What's going on?
-Mom!
-Da-rim.
My sister.
My little sister.
-Da-rim.
-You're okay.
You're okay…
Let's go.
All right.
Mr. Gong.
Da-rim told me
that you two are dating.
That's right.
I hope you don't take this the wrong way,
but you still
have no idea how truly great
a person Da-rim is.
She'll do anything and everything
for the people she cares about
and trusts them until the end.
That's the reason she's been hurt a lot
and holds onto a lot of pain.
But she doesn't show it like a fool.
I won't just stand by if you make her cry.
She's my family.
Please be good to her.
Please.
I hear you,
but I want you to know
that I like Da-rim
more than you think I do.
I'll never make her cry
or betray her.
So don't worry.
It's the pretty lady!
Did you sleep well?
How are you feeling?
I'm fine, thanks to you.
Hold on.
Da-rim's inside, right?
Let's go.
She's passed out.
Do you need her for something?
I have a morning appointment,
so I wanted to ask her
to take him to daycare.
I can do it.
Da-rim's going to need
at least three more days to sober up.
Let's go, Jun.
Why are you smiling?
Because I'm going to daycare
with the pretty lady.
You're so smart, unlike your dad.
Which kindergarten did you go to?
I never went to kindergarten or daycare.
My teachers came to my house.
Then when did you play with your friends?
I don't have friends.
I don't know how to make them either.
I guess this is why
early education is essential.
Then should I become your friend?
When someone asks you
who your best friend is,
tell them it's me.
Really?
Thank you, Jun.
Maybe I should join you at daycare.
Is it fun?
Preparing for the talent show
is fun and all, but…
But?
All the other kids
will have their moms there,
but I won't, and it doesn't feel good.
When's the talent show?
Good morning.
Hey there.
Nan-suk.
Why is your face so puffy?
Did someone hit you?
I had some instant noodles
and soju last night.
Customer service is no joke.
I'm burning up inside. Look at yourself.
It looks like you had a couple of bottles.
Oh, I also had a drink or two.
Hey, Go-eun.
She's completely out of it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It is what it is.
What can we do?
Everybody, good morning.
You're chipper this morning.
I know, right? Was your husband
extra nice to you or something?
No, as if.
I was professionally treated.
You went to see a doctor?
No, retail therapy.
Shopping is the best cure for stress.
Look at this.
This is expensive.
Doesn't it look luxurious?
-Good for you.
-Well done.
KINDNESS, DEDICATION
I see. Yes, of course.
So you're saying
you discovered a foreign substance
inside the diaper, correct?
I see.
All right. I submitted the complaint.
It wasn't just "a foreign substance."
It was a chicken bone.
Don't you hear me?
Did you not look at the photo?
I did look at it,
but something that big
would've caused our machinery to stop.
I'd say it's close to impossible
for something like that
to be missed during production.
Are you saying I'm lying right now?
No, ma'am. Not at all.
There could've been some sort of mishap.
-So how about--
-Forget it!
I want 100 million won in compensation.
The baby woke up again because of you!
It took forever for me to put it to sleep!
Take responsibility!
Yes, ma'am.
We'll first have someone visit you
and check the product in question.
Enough with the checking!
Are you looking down on me
because I'm a mom?
Just wait and see.
I won't let this slide!
No, I--
Hello?
Ms. Gong!
Ms. Gong, there's an emergency.
Please take a look at this.
What now?
A CHICKEN BONE IN A DIAPER
IGNORED BY NB CS "BECAUSE I'M A MOM"
What is this?
Chicken bone?
Chicken bone is one thing,
but this is the bigger issue.
You should at least send someone to check.
Our policy wouldn't permit compensation
because it was a mishap on your end.
Are you saying I'm lying?
Yes, that's exactly what I'm saying.
Are you looking down on me
because I'm a mom?
Probably.
What the hell? Who is this?
Well,
it sounds like Go Da-rim,
so I checked
the original recording of the call.
This audio is fake.
I think she manipulated it
with a deepfake or whatever.
Manipulated?
Yes. I'll have it removed immediately
for spreading false information
and issue a statement.
Go ahead.
Wait.
Did you say that was Go Da-rim's voice?
Yes.
-Delete the original recording.
-Pardon?
Delete the file.
Hello, Producer.
Have you been well?
-Boycott it!
-Chicken bone diaper!
The CS representative's remarks have
sparked public outrage among consumers,
and mom communities are now spreading
-a boycott movement against Natural BeBe.
-A foreign substance was discovered.
-Unapologetic corporate bully!
-It was none other than a chicken bone.
-Boycott it!
-The CS representative must be insane.
Apologize for that unacceptable service!
-Apologize!
-Guys!
-Excuse me.
-A diaper from a major company…
Please don't do this.
There's been a misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
The chicken bone or that insane employee?
The chicken bone hasn't been confirmed,
and I never said any of those things.
Hold on.
Are you that crazy bitch?
Yeah, that's her voice!
-Everyone, that's her.
-She has the face of a snake.
What misunderstanding?
We heard the recording.
No, that's not--
You still haven't come to your senses!
Get a grip!
Don't try to feed us that nonsense.
Are you serious right now?
Take this!
-How dare you?
-You piece of trash!
A chicken bone in a diaper?
I'm so pissed off right now.
Are we going to let them get away with it?
Come on out!
We need to tear this place down!
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Please move.
Make way.
Move.
My goodness. Is that your doing?
I thought I'd escalate it a bit.
An affair with the troublemaker
who's tarnishing the company's image.
That should be enough
to get rid of Gong Ji-hyeok.
Yeah.
I confirmed that they're dating.
Like father, like son.
Even affairs run in the family.
This should be enough
to get rid of him once and for all.
Before that,
take a look at this.
What's this?
My goodness.
Look at you.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
You just bought that coat.
Forget it. Who cares about that?
Why are they causing such a ruckus
when they don't even know the whole story?
I know.
We live in a scary world.
I submitted requests for the post to be
taken down, but it keeps getting reposted.
It feels like someone's
deliberately spreading it.
I can't believe this.
You're here.
I…
Are you hurt?
Everyone guarded me, so I'm fine.
-We'll take immediate legal action.
-No.
I want to go
and talk to her in person.
Who knows what she'll do to you?
Don't do anything.
I'll handle it.
She's my customer.
As a member of the Mother TF Team,
I have to solve my own problems.
That's taking responsibility.
Then I'll come with you.
Okay.
This is it.
Can I help you?
Are you Ms. Lee So-yeong?
Yes. Who are you?
Oh, hello. I'm Go Da-rim,
an employee of Natural BeBe.
We just came by
because we wanted to ask you
about the complaint you made.
How did you know where I live?
Did you leak my personal information?
It'd be a leak if we provided it
to a third party without your permission.
We lawfully used your personal information
for business purposes.
That doesn't matter!
You showed up unannounced.
-You kept ignoring our calls--
-Leave right now.
Or I'll report you for stalking.
Ma'am, just a moment.
Ma'am, wait.
Please talk to us.
Avoiding us and the issue
isn't going to solve anything.
What issue?
What do you want?
Do you know how much trouble
you've caused us?
Do I need to know?
That company has never once listened
to my troubles!
Please calm down.
Why don't we talk inside?
Oh no! Ye-eun!
Ye-eun!
The baby.
Oh no!
Is she okay?
I'm so sorry.
Mommy's so sorry.
Let's just get you admitted.
They said it was just a scratch.
It's nothing serious.
Do you know how many times
my heart dropped today?
Look at it. I'm fine.
What are we going to do about your wrist?
What do you mean? It's fine.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Is Ye-eun okay?
Yes, they said she was fine.
Thank goodness.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. No one got hurt.
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
My goodness.
I MANIPULATED THE NATURAL BEBE CONTROVERSY
I'm the person who posted
about the chicken bone incident
in Natural BeBe's diaper.
I'd like to confess
that I made all of it up
and offer my sincerest apologies.
I've been dealing
with some personal issues recently,
and I ended up taking it out
on an innocent employee at Natural BeBe.
Despite all that,
the CS representative
threw herself to save my baby
and was injured in the process.
I don't have the words to describe
how sorry and thankful I am.
To prove her innocence,
I've attached
the original recording of the call.
All right.
The media outlets
have agreed to issue corrections.
What about the rest?
We've uploaded an announcement
along with the original call recording.
We've released our official statement
on social media and online communities.
I've contacted
all the online mom communities as well,
and they've agreed to take down
all defamatory posts.
Yeah!
Well done, everyone.
-Good job, everyone!
-We're done.
-It's over now, Da-rim.
-Team dinner tonight?
How about a refreshing beer?
-That sounds so nice.
-Well done.
What should we eat?
-Grilled intestines.
-I don't know.
Ms. Go Da-rim.
How's your injury?
It's healing.
Is that so?
CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE STATUS
NAME: GO DA-RIM
STATUS: UNMARRIED
DYNAMITE KISS
You were right.
Ji-hyeok knows Go Da-rim is single.
If I didn't lie to get hired,
I'm sure
someone more qualified
would've gotten my spot.
I don't think I can continue working here.
I'm sorry.
How did you know about this?
Jun and I decided to become best friends.
Please don't give false hope to Jun.
I have no interest in you as a woman.
You basically made our team.
Stop running away now.
I won't ever let you go.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim